wercker.com 2018-09-25

# Privacy

_Wercker has been[ _acquired_](https://www.oracle.com/corporate/acquisitions/wercker/index.html) by [Oracle](https://www.wercker.com/about/oracle) and will soon transition to the Oracle Privacy Policy. Click [_here_](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/index.html) to view the Oracle Privacy Policy. Please note that the provisions of Wercker's Privacy Policy below will remain active until the policy transition is complete._

### General information

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Terms of Service](https://www.wercker.com/terms), or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Wercker is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Wercker will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Information gathering and usage

When you register for Wercker we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, or payment information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter any payment details. Wercker uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Wercker service. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to re-login to your Wercker account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

### Data storage

Wercker uses third-party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Wercker. Although Wercker owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Wercker application, you retain all rights to your data.

### Disclosure

Wercker may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the [Terms of Service](https://www.wercker.com/terms).

### Changes

Wercker may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Wercker primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Trademarks

All product names, logos, and brands are property of their respective owners. All company, product and service names used in this website are for identification purposes only. Use of these names, logos, and brands does not imply endorsement unless specified. 

### Questions

See [Oracle's Privacy Policy](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/privacy-policy.html) for more information.
